import { Topic } from '.'

export const Bootstrap: Topic = {
  topic: 'Bootstrap',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 300,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who developed Bootstrap?',
      choices: ['Twitter', 'Google', 'Facebook', 'GitHub'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Twitter'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Bootstrap is mainly used for:',
      choices: ['Styling web pages', 'Server-side scripting', 'Database design', 'Game development'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Styling web pages'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Bootstrap provides pre-built components.',
      choices: ['True', 'False'],
      type: 'boolean',
      correctAnswers: ['True'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following are Bootstrap components?',
      choices: ['Modal', 'Card', 'Button', 'Canvas'],
      type: 'MAQs',
      correctAnswers: ['Modal', 'Card', 'Button'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the default grid system in Bootstrap based on?',
      choices: ['12 columns', '10 columns', '8 columns', '16 columns'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['12 columns'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Bootstrap classes always start with a dot (.)',
      choices: ['True', 'False'],
      type: 'boolean',
      correctAnswers: ['True'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Bootstrap class centers text?',
      choices: ['.text-center', '.align-text-center', '.center-text', '.text-align-center'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['.text-center'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these are utility classes in Bootstrap?',
      choices: ['.mt-3', '.p-2', '.bg-primary', '.function()'],
      type: 'MAQs',
      correctAnswers: ['.mt-3', '.p-2', '.bg-primary'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Does Bootstrap use JavaScript?',
      choices: ['True', 'False'],
      type: 'boolean',
      correctAnswers: ['True'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Which class makes an element responsive in Bootstrap?',
      choices: ['.img-fluid', '.responsive', '.fluid-img', '.img-responsive'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['.img-fluid'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
};
